[The Epoch of Miyu]
[عصر ميو]
[Episode 6]
[الحلقة 6]
Alright, let's eat.
حسنا، دعونا نأكل.
Come on, let's eat.
هيا، دعونا نأكل.
Hurry up and get the duty staff from the executive floor.
عجلوا واحصلوا على الموظفين المناوبين من الطابق التنفيذي.
Now!
الآن!
Come on.
تعال.
Eat more.
تناول المزيد.
The baby needs to eat more too.
يحتاج الطفل إلى تناول المزيد أيضًا.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's have a drink.
دعونا نتناول مشروبًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Miyu.
ميو.
I've been looking for you.
لقد كنت أبحث عنك.
What is it, Ms. Zhang?
ما الأمر يا سيدة تشانغ؟
Private room 808 in the Chinese restaurant
غرفة خاصة 808 بالمطعم الصيني
needs a hand.
يحتاج إلى يد.
Can you head over?
هل يمكنك التوجه؟
But I'm already off work.
لكنني بالفعل خارج العمل.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But the others are busy and can't get away.
لكن الآخرين مشغولون ولا يستطيع الابتعاد.
Do me a favor.
افعل لي معروفا.
I'll pay you overtime.
سأدفع لك العمل الإضافي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll tidy up and go over.
سوف أقوم بالترتيب والذهاب.
[Happy Birthday to Dear Mom]
[عيد ميلاد سعيد لأمي العزيزة]
Come on, Mom.
هيا يا أمي.
Cheers to you.
تحياتي لك.
Happy 60th birthday.
عيد ميلاد سعيد الستين.
May your fortune be as vast as the East Sea,
نرجو أن تكون ثروتك واسعة كالبحر الشرقي
and your life as long as the Southern Mountains.
وحياتك طالما مثل الجبال الجنوبية .
-My son. -Wait.
-ابني. -انتظر.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Mom should be 16,
يجب أن يكون عمر أمي 16 عامًا،
not 60.
ليس 60.
You're so sweet.
أنت لطيف جدا.
Your daughter-in-law
زوجة ابنك
is such a sweet talker.
هو مثل هذا المتكلم الحلو.
Thanks to her,
شكرا لها،
the grandson we've been waiting for for years
الحفيد ننتظر منذ سنوات
is finally on the way.
هو في النهاية على الطريق.
[Happy Birthday to Dear Mom]
[عيد ميلاد سعيد لأمي العزيزة]
I'm so pleased.
أنا مسرور جدا.
Mom,
أمي،
how do you know it's a boy?
كيف تعرف أنه صبي؟
You're in great condition,
أنت في حالة رائعة،
even like a sister to me.
حتى مثل أخت لي.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
How can I help you?
كيف يمكنني مساعدك؟
Isn't this Miyu?
أليس هذا ميو؟
Sorry, I got the wrong room.
آسف، لقد حصلت على الغرفة الخطأ.
Stop right there!
توقف هناك!
Why are you running?
لماذا تركض؟
You took forever to get here.
لقد استغرقت وقتًا طويلاً للوصول إلى هنا.
Hurry up and come in to clean up.
أسرع وادخل للتنظيف.
Hurry!
عجل!
Mr. Feng,
السيد فنغ،
there's something else in the HSKP Department.
هناك شيء آخر في قسم HSKP.
How about I call...
ماذا عن أن أتصل...
No, you-
لا، أنت-
If she's busy,
إذا كانت مشغولة،
let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
Just get someone else.
مجرد الحصول على شخص آخر.
Follow Mr. Feng's instructions.
اتبع تعليمات السيد فنغ.
Mrs. Nie is right.
السيدة ني على حق.
Hurry up and clean in here.
اسرعوا ونظفوا هنا.
Whatever it is, deal with it later.
مهما كان الأمر، تعامل معه لاحقًا.
Change the bone dishes in front of the guests first.
تغيير أطباق العظام أمام الضيوف أولاً.
Now!
الآن!
How's the food?
كيف حال الطعام؟
Come on.
تعال.
Eat.
يأكل.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Mom, sit closer to me.
أمي، اجلسي بالقرب مني.
Don't get your clothes dirty.
لا تتسخ ملابسك.
Are you done eating?
هل انتهيت من الأكل؟
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Please pick it up.
يرجى استلامه.
Mom.
أم.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Sorry, Mom. I didn't mean it.
آسف يا أمي. لم أقصد ذلك.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
You made the floor so slippery!
لقد جعلت الأرضية زلقة جدًا!
I almost fell!
لقد سقطت تقريبا!
Yeah. Did you hear that?
نعم. هل سمعت ذلك؟
How do you work?
كيف تعمل؟
Aren't you going to hurry over and wipe it clean?
الن تذهب لتسرع وتمسحه نظيفًا؟
Apologize to the guests.
اعتذر للضيوف.
[Happy Birthday to Dear Mom]
[عيد ميلاد سعيد لأمي العزيزة]
Do you even want to work here?
هل تريد حتى العمل هنا؟
Go now!
اذهب الآن!
Why are you using a dirty towel to wipe my mom's clothes?
لماذا تستخدم منشفة قذرة لمسح ملابس أمي؟
Mr. Feng.
السيد فنغ.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Are your hotel attendants
هل مضيفات الفندق الخاص بك
all so careless?
كل ذلك الإهمال؟
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Do you still want to work here?
هل مازلت تريد العمل هنا؟
-Alright. -Forget it.
-على ما يرام. -انسى ذلك.
Listen to me,
إسمعني،
I didn't even hire this attendant.
أنا لم أستأجر حتى هذه المرافقة
I, Feng Kaixin,
أنا، فنغ كيكسين،
would never hire such a person
لن يوظف مثل هذا الشخص أبدًا
into our Purong Hotel.
في فندقنا Purong.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Didn't you say it?
لم لا تقول ذلك؟
She's from the HSKP Department.
إنها من قسم HSKP.
It's normal that she doesn't know how to do it.
من الطبيعي ذلك إنها لا تعرف كيف تفعل ذلك.
Just get someone else.
مجرد الحصول على شخص آخر.
You heard it.
لقد سمعت ذلك.
You're lucky
أنت محظوظ
the guest didn't hold you accountable.
الضيف لم يحاسبك.
Get out of here!
اخرج من هنا!
Have you forgotten
هل نسيت
♪ A flicker of dim light ♪
♪ وميض من الضوء الخافت ♪
about helping my ex-husband lie to me last time
بشأن مساعدة زوجي السابق كذب علي آخر مرة
so quickly?
بهذه السرعة؟
Thanks to you,
شكرا لك
♪ A bowl of warm soup ♪
♪ وعاء من الحساء الدافئ ♪
I'm not Mrs. Nie anymore.
أنا لست السيدة ني بعد الآن.
♪ People in the city ♪
♪ الناس في المدينة ♪
You just let her go like that?
هل تركتها تذهب هكذا؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
♪ Squeezing into the hustle and bustle ♪
♪ الضغط في الزحام والضجيج ♪
Could you at least say less?
هل يمكنك على الأقل أن تقول أقل؟
It's Mom's birthday.
إنه عيد ميلاد أمي.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
♪ The palms of time ♪
♪ كف الزمن ♪
♪ Grinding away the simple days ♪
♪ طحن الأيام البسيطة ♪
♪ Sprinkling them into this busy world ♪
♪ رشهم في هذا العالم المزدحم ♪
♪ To be tasted, bit by bit ♪
♪ ليتم تذوقه شيئًا فشيئًا ♪
♪ Embracing this radiant world ♪
♪ احتضان هذا العالم المشع ♪
♪ Keeps the heart from fading to grey ♪
♪ يحفظ القلب من الذبول إلى الشيب ♪
♪ Life's joy, sorrow, cold, and warmth ♪
♪ فرح الحياة وحزنها وبردها ودفءها ♪
-Sorry. -It's okay.
-آسف. -لا بأس.
Come on.
تعال.
Why bother?
لماذا تهتم؟
Don't get upset.
لا تنزعج.
♪ Intertwined within the mundane ♪
♪ متشابكة داخل الدنيوية ♪
It's my mom's birthday.
إنه عيد ميلاد أمي.
Come on, sit.
هيا، الجلوس.
♪ Let us bravely gather up ♪
♪ دعونا نجتمع بشجاعة ♪
I'll go to the restroom.
سأذهب إلى الحمام.
Help yourselves.
ساعدوا أنفسكم.
Okay.
تمام.
♪ The forgotten past ♪
♪ الماضي المنسي ♪
Well,
حسنًا،
one mere attendant
مجرد مرافق
messed up the atmosphere for everyone.
أفسدت الأجواء على الجميع.
♪ There may be regrets ♪
♪ قد يكون هناك ندم ♪
I'll fine myself with a drink.
سوف أكافئ نفسي بشراب.
Bottoms up.
قيعان تصل.
♪ There may be loneliness ♪
♪ قد يكون هناك شعور بالوحدة ♪
Okay, stop rushing me.
حسنًا، توقف عن التسرع بي.
I got the food.
حصلت على الطعام.
Five minutes.
خمس دقائق.
Three minutes, okay?
ثلاث دقائق، حسنًا؟
I promise-
أعدك-
About what happened just now.
حول ما حدث للتو.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I didn't know you were here.
لم أكن أعلم أنك هنا.
You care so much about other women.
أنت تهتم كثيرًا بالنساء الأخريات.
Won't your wife get mad?
ألن تغضب زوجتك؟
I don't care all that.
لا يهمني كل ذلك.
Seeing you like this
أراك هكذا
makes me
يجعلني
feel terrible.
أشعر بالفزع.
If you need help,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة،
I'll help you.
سأساعدك.
What's wrong with me like this now?
ما خطبي هكذا الآن؟
I make my own money to support myself.
أنا أكسب أموالي الخاصة لدعم نفسي.
Is it any more shameful than being your full-time nanny?
فهل هو أكثر خجلا من أن تكوني مربية أطفالك بدوام كامل؟
You don't have to speak so coldly.
ليس عليك أن تتحدث بهذه البرودة.
Yes. I admit it—we did get divorced.
نعم. أنا أعترف بذلك – لقد انفصلنا.
But to me,
لكن بالنسبة لي
you've always been family.
لقد كنت دائما العائلة.
And I still have some
ولا يزال لدي بعض
connections or resources
اتصالات أو موارد
in hotel marketing.
في التسويق الفندقي.
If you need them,
إذا كنت في حاجة إليها،
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
That's enough, Nie Yucheng.
هذا يكفي، ني يوتشنغ.
I appreciate your kindness,
أنا أقدر لطفك،
but I don't need anything.
لكنني لست بحاجة إلى أي شيء.
If there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Wait, I haven't finished. Can we talk?
انتظر، أنا لم أنتهي. أيمكننا أن تحدث؟
What are you two doing?
ماذا تفعلان؟
What are you afraid of?
ما الذي تخاف منه؟
Miyu. Miyu!
ميو. ميو!
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Honey.
عسل.
You went to the bathroom for so long.
لقد ذهبت إلى الحمام لفترة طويلة.
Isn't there one in the private room?
ألا يوجد واحد في الغرفة الخاصة؟
I have some things to discuss with her.
لدي بعض الأمور لأناقشها معها
I have nothing to discuss with you.
ليس لدي ما أناقشه معك.
Please take him away immediately.
يرجى أخذه بعيدا على الفور.
Xu Miyu,
شو ميو،
you and Nie Yucheng are in the past.
أنت وNie Yucheng في الماضي.
Can't you just part ways peacefully?
ألا يمكنك أن تفترق بسلام؟
Stop pestering my husband like this.
توقف عن مضايقة زوجي بهذه الطريقة.
This is already seriously
هذا بالفعل جدي
affecting our lives.
تؤثر على حياتنا.
Me pestering him?
من أضايقه؟
Why don't you ask your husband himself
لماذا لا تسألين زوجك بنفسه
why he cornered me here
لماذا حاصرني هنا
and what disgusting things he said to me?
وما الأشياء المقرفة التي قالها لي؟
Instead of wasting time messing with me,
بدلاً من إضاعة الوقت في العبث معي،
you should keep your own man in line.
يجب أن تبقي رجلك في الطابور.
Alright, stop making a scene.
حسنًا، توقف عن صنع المشهد.
Look at her attitude.
انظر إلى موقفها.
What kind of attitude is that?
أي نوع من الموقف هذا؟
Mr. Nie,
السيد ني،
Mrs. Nie.
السيدة ني.
Everyone in the room is looking for you.
الجميع في الغرفة يبحثون عنك.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go back.
دعونا نعود.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Miyu.
ميو.
[Dad]
[أبي]
What has your husband been busy with lately?
ما عند زوجك كنت مشغولا في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Why isn't he answering the phone?
لماذا لا يجيب على الهاتف؟
[Dad]
[أبي]
Why are you calling him?
لماذا تتصل به؟
To ask him to bring more customers to the guesthouse.
ليطلب منه أن يحضر المزيد من العملاء إلى دار الضيافة.
[Dad]
[أبي]
Don't call him anymore.
لا تتصل به بعد الآن.
[Dad Inviting You to Voice Chat]
[أبي يدعوك للمحادثة الصوتية]
Look,
انظر
she's getting more and more outrageous.
لقد أصبحت أكثر فأكثر فاحشة.
Not answering my calls anymore.
ولم يعد يرد على مكالماتي.
And she told me not to call Yucheng.
وأخبرتني ألا أتصل بـ Yucheng.
Do you think I want to call him?
هل تعتقد أنني أريد الاتصال به؟
If there were any other good way,
لو كان هناك أي طريقة جيدة أخرى،
would I need to beg her husband?
هل أحتاج إلى التسول لزوجها؟
Are they still having conflicts?
هل ما زالوا يواجهون صراعات؟
Why do I feel like Miyu has been acting weird lately?
لماذا أشعر لقد كان ميو يتصرف بغرابة في الآونة الأخيرة؟
She hasn't mentioned Nie Yucheng at all.
لم تذكر ني يوتشنغ على الإطلاق.
How big of a conflict
ما حجم الصراع
can those two have living together?
هل يمكن لهذين الاثنين العيش معًا؟
Besides,
علاوة على ذلك
even if Yucheng did something wrong,
حتى لو فعل Yucheng شيئًا خاطئًا،
a few words and it'd be over, right?
بضع كلمات وسوف ينتهي الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
They don't have to make a big scene.
ليس عليهم أن يصنعوا مشهدًا كبيرًا.
I'm just worried she's too
أنا فقط قلقة من أنها أيضًا
stubborn and doesn't get it.
عنيد ولا يحصل عليه.
Then how about...
ثم ماذا عن...
How about we go check on them?
ماذا عن أن نذهب للاطمئنان عليهم؟
Mom,
أمي،
let me drive you home.
دعني أقودك إلى المنزل
Zhenzhen has been busy all night
لقد كان Zhenzhen مشغولاً طوال الليل
and isn't feeling well.
وليس على ما يرام.
Should we take her to the hospital?
هل يجب أن نأخذها إلى المستشفى؟
Don't let it harm the baby.
لا تدع ذلك يؤذي الطفل.
No need.
لا حاجة.
She's just tired.
إنها متعبة فقط.
She'll be fine.
سوف تكون بخير.
Yucheng,
يوتشنغ،
I must remind you of something.
يجب أن أذكرك بشيء.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Zhenzhen is different from your ex-wife.
Zhenzhen يختلف عن زوجتك السابقة.
She's pregnant with our Nie family's child.
إنها حامل مع طفل عائلة ني لدينا.
It's time for you to settle down.
لقد حان الوقت لتستقر.
You must never let her down, understand?
يجب ألا تخذلها أبدًا، مفهوم؟
Mom, I know.
أمي، أعرف.
You can rest assured.
يمكنك أن تطمئن.
I'm going to be a father.
انا ذاهب ليكون أبا.
I'll definitely live a good life this time.
سأفعل بالتأكيد عش حياة طيبة هذه المرة.
That's more like it.
هذا أشبه ذلك.
Come on, I'll get you home.
هيا، سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
When you went to the Chinese restaurant yesterday,
عندما ذهبت الى المطعم الصيني أمس
[Customer Satisfaction Survey]
[استبيان رضا العملاء]
why did you end up getting a bad review?
لماذا انتهى بك الأمر بالحصول على مراجعة سيئة؟
I heard the guest was furious,
سمعت أن الضيف غاضب،
and complained for over 10 minutes.
وشكا لأكثر من 10 دقائق.
They even specifically
بل إنهم على وجه التحديد
marked your name on it.
وضعت اسمك عليها.
I heard
سمعت
you know this guest.
أنت تعرف هذا الضيف.
Who told you that?
من قال لك ذلك؟
Anyway,
على أي حال،
these kinds of specific complaints
هذه الأنواع من الشكاوى المحددة
are quite serious.
خطيرة للغاية.
You need to reflect on your work properly.
تحتاج إلى التفكير في عملك بشكل صحيح.
Miyu,
ميو،
that's your second bad review.
هذه هي المراجعة السيئة الثانية.
You have to take it seriously.
عليك أن تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد.
The legal wife being humiliated by the mistress?
الزوجة الشرعية التعرض للإهانة من قبل عشيقة؟
Is it really that dramatic?
هل الأمر دراماتيكي حقًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
And according to the HSKP Department,
وبحسب قسم HSKP
she caught them cheating on the executive floor.
لقد اشتعلت بهم وهم يغشون في الطابق التنفيذي.
Oh my.
يا بلدي.
And she's still working here as an attendant?
وما زالت العمل هنا كمضيف؟
Is she a masochist?
هل هي مازوشي؟
She has to make a living.
عليها أن تكسب لقمة العيش.
I heard
سمعت
she used to act like she owned this place not long ago,
كانت تتصرف مثل لقد امتلكت هذا المكان منذ وقت ليس ببعيد،
spending thousands in one night.
إنفاق الآلاف في ليلة واحدة.
What goes around comes around.
ما يدور حولها ويأتي حولها.
Didn't they say her ex-husband
ألم يقولوا زوجها السابق
has close ties with Purong?
لديه علاقات وثيقة مع بورونج؟
Maybe
ربما
she's playing the victim here on purpose
إنها تلعب دور الضحية هنا عن قصد
to find a chance to win back her ex-husband.
للعثور على فرصة لاستعادة زوجها السابق.
Sorry about that.
آسف لذلك.
What's wrong with her?
ما هو الخطأ معها؟
That's her.
هذه هي.
Did you hear about that person on the executive floor?
هل سمعت عن ذلك الشخص في الطابق التنفيذي؟
Yeah, I heard.
نعم سمعت.
-So many people are talking about it. -Divorced and came out to be an attendant.
-الكثير من الناس يتحدثون عن ذلك. - طلقت وخرجت لتكون حاضرة.
And then she just happened to run into
وبعد ذلك صادفت
her ex-husband's family coming to eat.
عائلة زوجها السابق قادمة لتناول الطعام.
It's so mortifying.
إنه أمر مخيف للغاية.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
-How could she still keep working here? -I definitely couldn't do it.
-كيف يمكنها الاستمرار في العمل هنا؟ -بالتأكيد لم أستطع فعل ذلك.
Did you hear she spent a lot of money before?
هل سمعت لقد أنفقت الكثير من المال من قبل؟
-Yeah, I heard. -And ended up here being an attendant.
-نعم سمعت. -وانتهى بي الأمر هنا ليكون مرافقا.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Our circle is just this samll.
دائرتنا هي مجرد هذه الصغيرة.
Starting today,
ابتداء من اليوم
I'll do every thing I want to do,
سأفعل كل ما أريد القيام به،
say every word I want to say.
أقول كل كلمة أريد أن أقول.
I won't be watching for your approval anymore.
لن أشاهد للحصول على موافقتك بعد الآن.
I won't care if you're happy or not.
لن أهتم إذا كنت سعيدًا أم لا.
I only care if I'm happy.
لا أهتم إلا إذا كنت سعيدًا.
I want to go back to 10 years ago,
أريد أن أعود إلى ما قبل 10 سنوات،
that turning point that changed my life,
نقطة التحول تلك التي غيرت حياتي،
to see if I can realize my value in life
لأرى إن كان بإمكاني إدراك قيمتي في الحياة
through my own efforts.
من خلال مجهوداتي الخاصة.
No matter how many lofty ambitions I have,
مهما كثرت طموحاتي السامية
they're ruthlessly shattered
لقد تحطموا بلا رحمة
along with my self-esteem
مع احترامي لذاتي
at this moment.
في هذه اللحظة.
Physical hardships
الصعوبات الجسدية
and mental pressure
والضغط النفسي
are gradually consuming my hopes for the future,
تستهلك تدريجيا آمالي في المستقبل،
making me gradually realize a cruel fact.
مما يجعلني أدرك تدريجيا حقيقة قاسية.
The me right now
أنا الآن
may have already lost the chance to start over.
قد يكون بالفعل فقدت الفرصة للبدء من جديد.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
[شقة موظفي فندق بورونج]
♪ Life is full of ♪
♪ الحياة مليئة ♪
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
♪ مفترق طرق لا يحصى ♪
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
[شقة موظفي فندق بورونج]
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
♪ طارد الفرح بشدة، وسوف يفلت منك ♪
♪ All those confusions ♪
♪ كل تلك الإلتباسات ♪
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
♪ لا إجابات ولا أسباب ♪
Everyone keeps moving forward without stopping.
الجميع يحتفظ المضي قدما دون توقف.
♪ Throwing ourselves into the tide of the unknown ♪
♪ رمي أنفسنا في مد المجهول ♪
Only me,
أنا فقط،
getting trapped in the same spot again and again.
الوقوع في المحاصرين في نفس المكان مرارا وتكرارا.
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat, yet still asleep ♪
♪ معرفة متى تتقدم أو تتراجع، ومع ذلك مازلت نائمًا ♪
I really want to run away,
أنا حقا أريد أن أهرب،
but I can't even find
لكني لا أستطيع حتى العثور على
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
♪ الاستعجال في النضج قبل أواننا ♪
a place for myself in such a big city,
مكان لنفسي في هذه المدينة الكبيرة،
♪ Sighing at partings, who meets whom at which crossing ♪
♪ تنهد عند الفراق، من يلتقي بمن في أي معبر ♪
♪ Busy and restless ♪
♪ مشغول ومضطرب ♪
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ لا رجعة ولا توقف ♪
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
♪ طريقنا – هل تراه الآن ♪
Are you running away?
هل أنت هارب؟
If you think that by giving up now,
إذا كنت تعتقد ذلك بالاستسلام الآن،
all your difficulties will disappear,
كل الصعوبات التي تواجهك سوف تختفي،
then cutting your losses in time is a good thing.
ثم خفض خسائرك في الوقت المناسب هو شيء جيد.
After all, your personality is too accommodating.
بعد كل شيء، شخصيتك مريح للغاية.
To do well in the hotel industry,
لتحقيق أداء جيد في صناعة الفنادق،
it's going to be tough.
سيكون الأمر صعبا.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
مرحبا، السيد جي.
Why are you still here?
لماذا لا تزال هنا؟
Working as usual.
العمل كالمعتاد.
Not leaving?
لا تغادر؟
Not leaving.
لا يغادر.
If I left on my own,
إذا تركت وحدي،
wouldn't that play right into someone's hands?
لن يكون هذا اللعب الحق في أيدي شخص ما؟
Also,
وأيضا
whether I'm suited for this work
هل أنا مناسب لهذا العمل
is not for others to decide.
ليس للآخرين أن يقرروا.
Thanks for today, Qin.
شكرا لهذا اليوم، تشين.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
We're neighbors,
نحن جيران،
and it's on the way.
وهو في الطريق.
Should we call Miyu again?
هل يجب أن نتصل بميو مرة أخرى؟
If she doesn't answer, she must still be asleep.
إذا لم تجب، لا بد أنها لا تزال نائمة.
Don't call her.
لا تتصل بها.
Doesn't your daughter go to work in the morning?
لا ابنتك الذهاب إلى العمل في الصباح؟
She never goes to work.
إنها لا تذهب إلى العمل أبدًا.
She can sleep as long as she wants.
يمكنها النوم بقدر ما تريد.
In their family,
في عائلتهم
our daughter is in charge,
ابنتنا هي المسؤولة،
and the son-in-law is responsible for making money.
وصهره هو المسؤول عن كسب المال.
Then your son-in-law is really something.
إذن صهرك هو حقًا شيء ما.
One person makes money
شخص واحد يجني المال
for two people to spend.
لشخصين لقضاء.
How much does he have to make?
كم لديه لجعل؟
Qin, let me tell you,
تشين، دعني أخبرك،
how much money he makes really isn't the main point.
كم من المال يكسب حقا ليست النقطة الرئيسية.
The key is that my son-in-law‘s
المفتاح هو أن صهري
biggest merit is that
أكبر ميزة هي أن
he's good to his wife.
انه جيد لزوجته.
Yes.
نعم.
He treats our Miyu
يعامل ميو لدينا
really well.
جيد حقا.
A harmonious family prospers.
تزدهر الأسرة المتناغمة.
Xu,
شو،
you're about to enjoy a good life.
أنت على وشك الاستمتاع بحياة جيدة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's talk later.
دعونا نتحدث لاحقا.
Okay.
تمام.
Okay, take this.
حسنًا، خذ هذا.
Thank you, Qin.
شكرا لك تشين.
-Bye. -Thanks.
-الوداع. -شكرًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Bye.
الوداع.
Here, let me take this.
هنا، اسمحوا لي أن آخذ هذا.
How about we call Miyu again?
ماذا عن أن نتصل بـ Miyu مرة أخرى؟
We're already at the door.
نحن بالفعل عند الباب.
Why call?
لماذا الاتصال؟
Just enter it.
فقط أدخله.
You know the code.
أنت تعرف الرمز.
Come in.
ادخل.
Honey,
عسل،
did you forget...
هل نسيت...
Who are you?
من أنت؟
How did you get in?
كيف دخلت؟
You...
أنت...
Where's my phone?
أين هاتفي؟
Get out.
اخرج.
Get out!
اخرج!
This is my daughter's house.
هذا منزل ابنتي.
Why can't we come in?
لماذا لا نستطيع الدخول؟
Right.
يمين.
I haven't even asked who you are.
أنا لم أسأل حتى من أنت.
It's my daughter's house.
إنه منزل ابنتي.
You...
أنت...
What's she busy with?
ما هي مشغولة؟
Her own house has been...
كان منزلها...
She's not answering.
إنها لا تجيب.
Keep calling.
استمر في الاتصال.
What now?
ماذا الآن؟
Have you sorted it out?
هل قمت بتسوية الأمر؟
Your daughter has been kicked out.
لقد تم طرد ابنتك.
Now I'm the mistress of this house.
الآن أنا سيدة هذا المنزل.
[Marriage Certificate]
[وثيقة زواج]
You slut!
أنت وقحة!
You...
أنت...
Don't you dare!
لا تجرؤ!
If you dare do anything,
إذا كنت تجرأت على فعل أي شيء،
I'll sue you for trespassing.
سأقاضيك بتهمة التعدي على ممتلكات الغير.
Well,
حسنًا،
Lu Zhenzhen.
لو تشن تشن.
Look,
انظر
it's not easy
الأمر ليس سهلاً
for us to come all this way.
بالنسبة لنا أن نأتي كل هذا الطريق.
This is
هذا
the only home we have in Shanghai.
المنزل الوحيد الذي لدينا في شنغهاي.
If we don't see our daughter
إذا لم نرى ابنتنا
and clear this up today,
ووضح هذا اليوم،
we won't leave.
لن نغادر.
Right.
يمين.
You want to see your daughter?
هل تريد رؤية ابنتك؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll give you a ride.
سأعطيك توصيلة.
Okay.
تمام.
Your daughter is in there.
ابنتك هناك.
Go find her yourself.
اذهب وابحث عنها بنفسك
How did that slut know Miyu lived here?
كيف عرفت تلك الفاسقة أن ميو تعيش هنا؟
What's the relationship between them?
ما العلاقة بينهما؟
Could she be tricking us?
هل يمكن أن تخدعنا؟
I just forgot to ask.
لقد نسيت أن أسأل.
Which room does Miyu live in?
في أي غرفة يعيش ميو؟
How long will it take to check every single room?
كم من الوقت سوف يستغرق للتحقق من كل غرفة على حدة؟
Let's go ask.
دعنا نذهب نسأل.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Mom.
أم.
Miyu!
ميو!
Dad.
أب.
Miyu.
ميو.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
You...
أنت...
How...
كيف...
How come...
ازاي...
Come in.
ادخل.
Black Card Ji's room.
غرفة بلاك كارد جي.
Why are you dressed like this?
لماذا ترتدي مثل هذا؟
W-Why aren't you staying at home?
ث-لماذا لا تبقى في المنزل؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I was planning to
كنت أخطط ل
tell you about this later.
أخبرك عن هذا لاحقا.
Tell us what?
أخبرنا ماذا؟
There are wedding photos up on the wall.
هناك صور الزفاف على الحائط.
Even if I want to pull that slut's hair,
حتى لو أردت لسحب شعر تلك الفاسقة،
the police wouldn't help me.
الشرطة لن تساعدني.
Xu Miyu.
شو ميو.
Room 1809 is calling.
الغرفة 1809 تتصل.
Okay, got it.
حسنًا، فهمت.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Hurry up and come home with me.
اسرع وتعال معي إلى المنزل.
We will stand up for you.
سوف نقف من أجلك.
We're taking this home back right now.
نحن نعيد هذا المنزل الآن.
Mom.
أم.
-That's not my home anymore! -Let's go.
-هذا ليس منزلي بعد الآن! -دعنا نذهب.
Not your home?
ليس منزلك؟
Whose home is it then?
منزل من هو إذن؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Mr. Ji.
السيد جي.
My parents came to see me.
جاء والدي لرؤيتي.
I'll let them leave first.
سأسمح لهم بالمغادرة أولاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Go now.
اذهب الآن.
Go.
يذهب.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
Don't bring personal matters to work.
لا تجلب الأمور الشخصية إلى العمل.
Take the meal coupon.
خذ قسيمة الوجبة.
[Executive Lounge Meal Coupon]
[قسيمة وجبة الصالة التنفيذية]
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
I've already eaten.
لقد أكلت بالفعل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
[Executive Lounge Meal Coupon]
[قسيمة وجبة الصالة التنفيذية]
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Here.
هنا.
Here, have some.
هنا، لديك بعض.
Take this.
خذ هذا.
Did Nie Yucheng cheat on you?
هل خدعك ني يوتشنغ؟
He cheated and still has the nerve to bring up divorce?
لقد خدع وما زال لديه الجرأة لطرح الطلاق؟
I'm the one who wanted the divorce.
أنا من أراد الطلاق.
Have you lost your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
Miyu.
ميو.
Xiumei.
Xiumei.
Keep it down.
أبقِ الأمر منخفضًا.
Mind your image.
اهتم بصورتك.
You're his wife.
أنت زوجته.
He cheated on you.
لقد خدعك.
Why did you ask for a divorce?
لماذا طلبت الطلاق؟
You married him first.
لقد تزوجته أولاً.
Why would you give in to that slut?
لماذا تستسلم لتلك العاهرة؟
Mom,
أمي،
this isn't about who came first.
هذا لا يتعلق بمن جاء أولاً.
Is that slut pregnant?
هل تلك العاهرة حامل؟
Seriously, look at you.
على محمل الجد، انظر إليك.
Look at the mess you've made.
انظر إلى الفوضى التي أحدثتها.
Our divorce has nothing to do
طلاقنا ليس له علاقة
with children
مع الاطفال
or the other woman.
أو المرأة الأخرى.
I don't have any feelings for Nie Yucheng anymore.
ليس لدي أي مشاعر لـ Nie Yucheng بعد الآن.
I can't go on living like this.
لا أستطيع الاستمرار في العيش بهذه الطريقة.
Miyu,
ميو،
everything in the world needs to be managed.
كل شيء في العالم يحتاج إلى إدارة.
It's like growing crops.
انها مثل زراعة المحاصيل.
When it comes to drought or flood, you have to find a way.
عندما يتعلق الأمر بالجفاف أو الفيضانات، عليك أن تجد طريقة.
Don't be penny-wise
لا تكن حكيماً
and pound-foolish.
والجنيه أحمق.
Of course,
بالطبع
if you're determined to get a divorce
إذا كنت مصممة على الحصول على الطلاق
and never look back,
ولا تنظر إلى الوراء أبدًا،
that's fine too.
هذا جيد جدا.
Mom and Dad support you.
أمي وأبي يدعمونك.
Let's have a good talk.
دعونا نتحدث جيدا.
How do you plan to support yourself after the divorce?
كيف تخطط لدعم نفسك بعد الطلاق؟
I divided the marital property with him.
قسمت الممتلكات الزوجية معه.
Right.
يمين.
So how was it divided?
فكيف تم تقسيمها؟
We have agreed.
لقد اتفقنا.
Half of the money goes to each of us.
نصف المال يذهب إلى كل واحد منا.
His parents bought the house before we got married,
والديه اشتريت البيت قبل أن نتزوج،
so I don't want it.
لذلك أنا لا أريد ذلك.
I don't know how to drive,
لا أعرف القيادة،
so the car is useless to me.
وبالتالي فإن السيارة عديمة الفائدة بالنسبة لي.
Then,
ثم
doesn't it mean you gave everything to him?
لا يعني ذلك أعطيته كل شيء؟
You've taken a huge loss in the past 10 years.
لقد تعرضت لخسارة فادحة في السنوات العشر الماضية.
Stop for now.
توقف الآن.
Let me talk to her.
دعني أتحدث معها.
Okay.
تمام.
So,
إذن،
the house and the car go to him.
المنزل والسيارة يذهبان إليه.
What about the money?
ماذا عن المال؟
How much money did you get?
كم من المال حصلت عليه؟
Nie Yucheng earns millions a year, right?
يكسب ني يوتشنغ الملايين سنويًا، أليس كذلك؟
You should get
يجب أن تحصل على
at least 8 or 10 million.
على الأقل 8 أو 10 ملايين.
Let's invest this money in the guesthouse
دعونا نستثمر هذه الأموال في دار الضيافة
and other businesses too.
وغيرها من الشركات أيضا.
Then I think
ثم أعتقد
your life will be secured.
سيتم تأمين حياتك.
What do you think, Miyu?
ما رأيك، ميو؟
He invested the money.
لقد استثمر المال.
And lost it.
وخسرها.
How much did he lose?
كم خسر؟
He lost it all.
لقد خسر كل شيء.
All?
الجميع؟
Then...
ثم...
Then after all this,
ثم بعد كل هذا
doesn't it mean
لا يعني
you didn't get a penny?
لم تحصل على فلسا واحدا؟
Dad,
أبي،
Mom,
أمي،
my job is a bit tiring now,
عملي متعب بعض الشيء الآن،
but I earn my own money and spend it.
لكني أكسب أموالي الخاصة وأنفقها.
I feel at ease.
أشعر بالراحة.
It's just that I might not be able to pay off
انها مجرد أنني قد لا تكون قادرة على سداد
the online loan of 300,000 lately.
القرض عبر الإنترنت بقيمة 300000 مؤخرًا.
What kind of meat is this?
أي نوع من اللحوم هذا؟
It's so chewy.
انها مطاطية جدا.
Looks good but tastes bad.
تبدو جيدة ولكن طعمها سيء.
Look at you.
أنظر إليك.
Seriously,
على محمل الجد،
why did you mention paying off the debt?
لماذا ذكرت سداد الدين؟
Look.
ينظر.
Miyu.
ميو.
Room 1826.
غرفة 1826.
The guest wants two more bottles of mineral water.
الضيف يريد اثنين آخرين زجاجات من المياه المعدنية.
Okay.
تمام.
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
Mom,
أمي،
show Dad around the nearby mall.
أظهر لأبي حول المركز التجاري القريب.
I'll find you after work.
سأجدك بعد العمل.
Take some food.
خذ بعض الطعام.
Look, you've lost so much weight recently.
انظر، لقد فقدت الكثير من الوزن مؤخرًا.
I'm going.
انا ذاهب.
Eat it.
أكله.
Xu!
شو!
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Miyu told me to
قال لي ميو
show you around the mall.
تظهر لك في جميع أنحاء المركز التجاري.
Miyu has suffered so much grievance.
لقد عانت Miyu الكثير من التظلم.
What's there to show around?
ما هو هناك لتظهر حولها؟
Just wait here.
فقط انتظر هنا.
I'm going to take care of something.
سأعتني بشيء ما.
You...
أنت...
Hello.
مرحبًا.
[Private Customization: Explore Russia]
[التخصيص الخاص: اكتشف روسيا]
Miss.
آنسة
I'm looking for Nie Yucheng.
أنا أبحث عن ني يوتشنغ.
Have you made an appointment?
هل حددت موعدا؟
Just tell him his father-in-law is here.
فقط أخبريه أن والد زوجته هنا.
[Private Customization: Explore Russia]
[التخصيص الخاص: اكتشف روسيا]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Someone is at the door looking for Mr. Nie,
شخص ما عند الباب أبحث عن السيد ني،
saying he's his father-in-law.
قائلا انه والد زوجته.
Okay.
تمام.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Mr. Nie is very busy today.
السيد ني مشغول للغاية اليوم.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Mr. Nie is busy every day.
السيد ني مشغول كل يوم.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I...
أنا...
I'll wait for him.
سأنتظره.
Let him do his things.
دعه يفعل أشياءه.
You're Nie Yucheng's colleagues, right?
أنتم زملاء Nie Yucheng، أليس كذلك؟
I'm his father-in-law.
أنا والد زوجته.
I'll just wait for him here.
سأنتظره هنا فحسب.
Go on with your work.
استمر في عملك.
Keqi,
كيكي،
this person refuses to leave.
هذا الشخص يرفض المغادرة.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
[Changyang Travel Agency]
[وكالة سفريات تشانغيانغ]
Dad.
أب.
Yucheng!
يوتشنغ!
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Am I interrupting your work?
هل أقاطع عملك؟
No. Come over to the office.
لا، تعال إلى المكتب.
I told them no rush.
قلت لهم لا تتعجل.
Let's talk after you're done with work.
دعنا نتحدث بعد الانتهاء من العمل.
I have plenty of time.
لدي متسع من الوقت.
You should have called me.
كان يجب أن تتصل بي.
So I could pick you up.
حتى أتمكن من اصطحابك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
We had nothing to do at home anyway.
لم يكن لدينا ما نفعله في المنزل على أي حال.
Well,
حسنًا،
our neighbor happened to be driving
صادف أن جارنا كان يقود سيارته
to Shanghai for goods,
إلى شنغهاي للبضائع،
so your mom and I hitched a ride with him
لذلك ركبنا أنا وأمك معه
to come check on you.
ليأتي للاطمئنان عليك.
Dad,
أبي،
I'm ashamed.
أشعر بالخجل.
I've been quite busy lately
لقد كنت مشغولاً للغاية في الآونة الأخيرة
and haven't had time to tell you about many things.
ولم يكن لدي الوقت لأخبرك عن أشياء كثيرة.
There's no need.
ليست هناك حاجة.
We already know about
نحن نعرف بالفعل عن
what happened between you and Miyu.
ماذا حدث بينك وبين ميو.
I'm sorry, Dad.
أنا آسف يا أبي.
This is my fault.
هذا هو خطأي.
Since you chose to separate,
بما أنك اخترت الانفصال،
you must have your own difficulties.
يجب أن يكون لديك الصعوبات الخاصة بك.
Anyway,
على أية حال،
Yucheng,
يوتشنغ،
you were husband and wife after all.
لقد كنت زوجًا وزوجة بعد كل شيء.
Even if the love is gone,
حتى لو ذهب الحب
the gratitude is still there, right?
الامتنان لا يزال موجودا، أليس كذلك؟
Look at you, a real social elite,
انظروا إليكم أيتها النخبة الاجتماعية الحقيقية،
a successful man
رجل ناجح
earning millions a year.
كسب الملايين سنويا.
Now that you're divorced,
الآن بعد أن كنت مطلقة،
you're being so stingy with your wife.
أنت بخيل جدًا مع زوجتك.
Doesn't that look bad to you?
ألا يبدو ذلك سيئًا بالنسبة لك؟
Look at you.
أنظر إليك.
Your have a big office
لديك مكتب كبير
and manage so many people.
وإدارة الكثير من الناس.
You can just offer some money
يمكنك فقط عرض بعض المال
and make it a decent breakup.
وجعله تفكك لائق.
Can't you do that?
لا يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك؟
Dad, you've misunderstood me.
أبي، لقد أسأت فهمي.
I really have no money.
أنا حقا ليس لدي المال.
When we divorced,
عندما طلقنا
I was deep in debt.
لقد كنت غارقًا في الديون.
Of course, I made it very clear to Miyu
بالطبع، لقد أوضحت الأمر بشكل واضح لميو
that she doesn't need to deal with repaying the debt.
أنها لا تحتاج إلى ذلك التعامل مع سداد الديون.
But honestly,
لكن بصراحة
I really don't have any extra money.
أنا حقا ليس لدي أي أموال إضافية.
Nie Yucheng,
ني يوتشنغ،
those words of yours
كلماتك تلك
can only fool a child.
يمكن أن يخدع الطفل فقط.
What?
ماذا؟
You fooled my girl and now you want to keep fooling me?
لقد خدعت فتاتي والآن تريد الاستمرار في خداعي؟
Dad, what are you talking about?
أبي، ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
How am I fooling you?
كيف أخدعك؟
Stop pretending with me.
توقف عن التظاهر معي.
The door is closed,
الباب مغلق
the curtains are drawn,
أسدلت الستائر
and there's nobody else here.
وليس هناك أحد آخر هنا.
My daughter
ابنتي
has been
لقد كان
with you for so many years.
معك لسنوات عديدة.
You have to compensate for her loss, right?
عليك أن تعوض لخسارتها، أليس كذلك؟
Fine.
بخير.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
How do you want me to compensate?
كيف تريدني أن أعوض؟
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
we used to be family.
اعتدنا أن نكون عائلة.
Let's settle it by year.
دعونا تسويتها حسب السنة.
200,000
200,000
for one year.
لمدة سنة واحدة.
Miyu served you for 10 years.
لقد خدمك ميو لمدة 10 سنوات.
That's 2 million in total.
هذا هو 2 مليون في المجموع.
You settle this money with me,
قمت بتسوية هذا المال معي،
and I'll leave immediately.
وسأغادر على الفور.
We will never see each other again.
لن نرى بعضنا البعض مرة أخرى.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
even if you earn hundreds of millions a year,
حتى لو كنت تكسب مئات الملايين سنويا،
it has nothing to do with our family.
لا علاقة له بعائلتنا.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
To be honest,
بصراحة،
this is the first time I've seen
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أرى فيها
a father selling his daughter so righteously.
أب يبيع ابنته بحق ذلك.
I sell my daughter?
أبيع ابنتي؟
It's not like you're any better.
ليس الأمر وكأنك أفضل.
You were two-timing
لقد كنت في توقيتين
and being ungrateful.
ويكون جاحدًا.
You're totally a cheating bastard.
أنت لقيط الغش تماما.
No.
رقم
No, well,
لا، حسنًا،
you need to be clear about this.
عليك أن تكون واضحا بشأن هذا.
Your daughter and I
أنا وبنتك
are already divorced.
مطلقات بالفعل.
It's in black and white,
باللونين الأبيض والأسود،
nationally certified.
معتمدة وطنيا.
No matter where you sue me,
لا يهم أين تقاضيني،
we have to follow the law, right?
علينا أن نتبع القانون، أليس كذلك؟
All in all,
على العموم،
you just don't want to give the money today.
أنت فقط لا تريد لإعطاء المال اليوم.
I've told you many times.
لقد قلت لك عدة مرات.
I really have no money.
أنا حقا ليس لدي المال.
What a coincidence.
يا لها من صدفة.
I just received a project bonus of 20,000.
لقد تلقيت للتو مكافأة للمشروع قدرها 20.000.
[Minfu Bank Transaction Alert]
[تنبيه بشأن معاملة بنك Minfu]
And a balance of 6,000.
والرصيد 6000.
26,000.
26000.
Will that work for you?
هل هذا مناسب لك؟
Nie Yucheng,
ني يوتشنغ،
you earn millions a year,
تكسب الملايين سنوياً،
and you give me 26,000?
وتعطيني 26000؟
Are you trying to brush me off like a beggar?
هل تحاول لتتجاهلني مثل المتسول؟
If you think it's too little,
إذا كنت تعتقد أنه قليل جدًا،
you can choose not to take it.
يمكنك اختيار عدم تناوله.
Fine.
بخير.
Then I'll go to the reception, the lobby,
ثم سأذهب إلى الاستقبال، الردهة،
and the hallway,
والممر
and ask someone else.
واسأل شخص آخر.
I have no money,
ليس لدي مال،
but I have tours.
ولكن لدي جولات.
Our company
شركتنا
has several tours ready to depart.
لديها عدة جولات جاهزة للمغادرة.
They're all big ones.
كلهم كبار.
Take your pick.
اختر ما يناسبك.
As for the profit,
أما الربح
you'll get the highest percentage.
سوف تحصل على أعلى نسبة.
Do you want it?
هل تريد ذلك؟
[Changyang Travel Agency Suzhou Tour Participant Information Sheet]
[جولة وكالة سفريات تشانغيانغ سوتشو ورقة معلومات المشارك]
Yes.
نعم.
I'll take them all.
سوف آخذهم جميعا.
Deal.
اتفاق.
What?
ماذا؟
He just gave you 26,000 and brushed you off?
لقد أعطاك للتو 26000 وتجاهلتك؟
That Nie guy is so cold-blooded.
هذا الرجل ني هو بدم بارد جدا.
I'm going to settle the score with him.
سأقوم بتصفية الحساب معه.
The divorce is already done.
لقد تم الطلاق بالفعل.
It won't be that easy to get money.
لن يكون من السهل الحصول على المال.
You want to settle the score?
هل تريد تصفية النتيجة؟
Even if you say you're his mother-in-law,
حتى لو قلت أنت حماته،
he won't acknowledge you.
لن يعترف بك.
Miyu served him faithfully for 10 years,
خدمه ميو بإخلاص لمدة 10 سنوات،
and only got 26,000?
وحصلت على 26000 فقط؟
If I had known this would happen,
لو كنت أعلم أن هذا سيحدث،
we should have come earlier.
كان ينبغي لنا أن نأتي في وقت سابق.
If we didn't get what we want from him,
فإن لم نحصل منه على ما نريد،
we wouldn't have allowed the divorce.
لم نكن لنسمح بالطلاق
What's the point of saying this now?
ما الفائدة من قول هذا الآن؟
What about the 300,000 we still owe?
ماذا عن الـ 300 ألف التي مازلنا مدينون بها؟
What can we do?
ماذا يمكننا أن نفعل؟
The son-in-law is gone,
ذهب الصهر،
so we go to our daughter.
لذلك نذهب إلى ابنتنا.
Let Miyu find a way to cover it for now.
دع Miyu يجد طريقة لتغطيته في الوقت الحالي.
That's all we can do.
هذا كل ما يمكننا القيام به.
Mrs. Nie,
السيدة ني،
you were a top sales rep at Yuhua before.
لقد كنت مندوب مبيعات كبير في Yuhua من قبل.
I hope you can bring more
أتمنى أن تتمكن من جلب المزيد
honor to our department after you join Purong.
شرف لقسمنا بعد انضمامك إلى Purong.
Mr. Qian,
السيد تشيان،
I will definitely work hard
بالتأكيد سأعمل بجد
and not let you down.
ولا نخذلكم.
You have a meeting later, right?
لديك اجتماع لاحقاً، أليس كذلك؟
Please stay.
يرجى البقاء.
I'll go to the parking lot by myself.
سأذهب إلى موقف السيارات بنفسي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Take care, Mrs. Nie.
اعتني بنفسك، سيدة ني.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Stop right there.
توقف هناك.
Stop!
قف!
Stop right there!
توقف هناك!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You tell me.
أخبرني أنت.
You slut!
أنت وقحة!
Homewrecker!
هادم المنزل!
You stole someone's husband and now you're asking me?
لقد سرقت زوج شخص ما والآن أنت تسألني؟
My daughter is good-tempered.
ابنتي ذات مزاج جيد.
She won't argue with you.
لن تتجادل معك.
But let me tell you,
لكن دعني أخبرك،
as her mother, I'm not done with you.
كوالدتها، أنا لم أنتهي منك.
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Be careful. I'll sue you for defamation.
احرص. سأقاضيك بتهمة التشهير.
You sue me for defamation?
هل تقاضيني بتهمة التشهير؟
Fine.
بخير.
Go ahead and sue me.
المضي قدما ومقاضاة لي.
Let's make things clear.
دعونا نجعل الأمور واضحة.
Tell me,
أخبرني
didn't you do all those shameless things?
لم تفعل كل تلك الأشياء المخزية؟
I'm warning you.
أنا أحذرك.
It's a fact that your daughter is divorced.
إنها حقيقة أن ابنتك مطلقة.
Don't act like a mother-in-law anymore,
لا تتصرفي كحماتك بعد الآن،
spouting nonsense
هراء
and making a scene.
وصنع مشهد.
Starting now,
ابتداءً من الآن،
if you say even one more personal insult to me,
إذا قلت حتى واحدا آخر إهانة شخصية لي،
I will sue you.
سأقاضيك.
Sue me then! Sue me!
مقاضاة لي ثم! مقاضاة لي!
Stealing someone's husband, you still have the nerve to sue?
سرقة زوج شخص ما, لا يزال لديك الجرأة لرفع دعوى؟
You're making wild accusations with no evidence.
أنت توجه اتهامات جامحة بدون أي دليل.
You two are just desperate because you can't leech off us anymore.
أنتما يائسان فقط لأنك لا تستطيع أن تعلق علينا بعد الآن.
You freeloaded off my husband for 10 years and still aren't satisfied.
لقد تحررت من زوجي لمدة 10 سنوات ومازلت غير راضٍ.
Shame on you.
عار عليك.
Miyu,
ميو،
it's from the receptionist.
إنها من موظفة الاستقبال
Miyu.
ميو.
Who-Who...
من-من...
Security! Security!
حماية! حماية!
You steal someone's husband and...
تسرق زوج شخص ما و...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
If I were you,
لو كنت أنت
I wouldn't go over there.
لن أذهب إلى هناك.
They're not your parents.
إنهم ليسوا والديك.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
If you go now,
إذا ذهبت الآن،
it will only make things worse.
فإنه لن يؤدي إلا إلى تفاقم الأمور.
No matter how bad it gets,
مهما ساء الأمر،
I won't just leave my parents.
لن أترك والدي فقط.
Do you know what's going on?
هل تعرف ماذا يحدث؟
-Let go! -What?
-اتركه! -ماذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
Seriously.
بجد.
Sir,
سيدي
it's a misunderstanding. Sorry.
إنه سوء فهم. آسف.
Please let them go.
من فضلك دعهم يذهبون.
Mom, stop making a scene here.
أمي، توقفي عن خلق مشهد هنا.
Don't stop me.
لا توقفني.
I need to settle the score with her. It's not over.
أنا بحاجة لتصفية الحساب معها. لم ينته الأمر.
That's right, Xu Miyu.
هذا صحيح، شو ميو.
Don't be in a rush to leave.
لا تتعجل في المغادرة.
We haven't settled our score yet.
لم نحسم حساباتنا بعد.
I have nothing to say to you.
ليس لدي ما أقوله لك.
Why are you so angry?
لماذا أنت غاضب جدا؟
We're colleagues now.
نحن زملاء الآن.
We'll be seeing a lot of each other.
سنرى الكثير من بعضنا البعض.
Don't make things so tense.
لا تجعل الأمور متوترة للغاية.
Why colleag-
لماذا زميل-
I still have to thank you
لا يزال يتعين علي أن أشكرك
for scheming so hard before
للتخطيط بجد من قبل
to get me out of Yuhua.
ليخرجني من يوهوا.
Otherwise,
وإلا
I wouldn't have gotten a better job.
لم أكن لأحصل على وظيفة أفضل.
Right?
يمين؟
Your job lost has nothing to do with me.
فقدان وظيفتك لا علاقة له بي.
I'm not interested in your affairs either.
أنا لست مهتمًا بشؤونك أيضًا.
Drawing a line with me so soon?
رسم خط معي قريبا جدا؟
Then when you told your dad to ask my husband for money,
ثم عندما أخبرت والدك لأطلب من زوجي المال،
why didn't you draw a clear line?
لماذا لم ترسم خطا واضحا؟
No, you-
لا، أنت-
Dad,
أبي،
what is she talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
No, I just wanted to...
لا، أردت فقط أن...
Still playing innocent?
لا تزال تلعب الأبرياء؟
You guys
يا شباب
snatched 6 deals all at once from my husband.
خطف 6 صفقات دفعة واحدة من زوجي.
Even the little bonus he just got
حتى المكافأة الصغيرة التي حصل عليها للتو
was all taken by you.
تم أخذ كل شيء بواسطتك.
You're really robbing under the guise of begging.
أنت تسرق حقا تحت ستار التسول.
Xu Miyu, I'm impressed.
شو ميو، أنا معجب.
On the surface, you act so pure and refined,
على السطح، أنت تتصرف بشكل نقي ومصقول،
but turn around and have your parents ask your ex-husband for money.
ولكن استدر واطلب من والديك اطلب من زوجك السابق المال.
You really want everything, don't you?
أنت حقا تريد كل شيء، أليس كذلك؟
Dad,
أبي،
did you go see Nie Yucheng?
هل ذهبت لرؤية ني يوتشنغ؟
Didn't I tell you not to look for him?
ألم أخبرك ألا تبحث عنه؟
I have nothing to do with him now.
ليس لدي أي علاقة معه الآن.
Aren't you making
ألست تصنع
a fool of yourself going to him now?
أحمق من نفسك الذهاب إليه الآن؟
I just wanted to help you.
أردت فقط مساعدتك.
You really...
أنت حقاً...
How can you have no conscience?
كيف لا يكون لديك ضمير؟
It was Nie Yucheng
لقد كان ني يوتشنغ
who cheated on you
من خانك
and let our whole family down.
وخذلان عائلتنا بأكملها.
Your dad went to get justice for you.
لقد ذهب والدك لتحقيق العدالة لك.
How could you scold him?
كيف يمكنك توبيخه؟
And her. She...
وهي. هي...
She stole your man.
لقد سرقت رجلك.
You don't blame her but blame us instead.
أنت لا تلومها بل تلومنا بدلاً من ذلك.
You really have no conscience. You...
ليس لديك حقا أي ضمير. أنت...
Mom, I didn't mean it that way.
أمي، لم أقصد ذلك بهذه الطريقة.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
You're taking an outsider's side.
أنت تأخذ جانبًا خارجيًا.
We're helping you.
نحن نساعدك.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
It's shot more clearly here.
لقد تم تصويرها بشكل أكثر وضوحًا هنا.
We're helping you.
نحن نساعدك.
Alright, stop talking.
حسنًا، توقف عن الحديث.
You blame me, huh?
أنت تلومني، هاه؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll just pretend
سأتظاهر فقط
I never raised you as my daughter, okay?
لم أقم بتربيتك أبدًا على أنك ابنتي، حسنًا؟
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Hey, don't...
مهلا، لا...
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
Dad! Mom!
أب! أم!
What a family of drama queens.
يا لها من عائلة ملكات الدراما.
I should set up a stage for you.
يجب أن أقوم بإعداد مسرح لك.
Lu Zhenzhen, I'm warning you.
لو زينتشن، أنا أحذرك.
Stop staring at other people's lives.
التوقف عن التحديق في حياة الآخرين.
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
Dad, Mom!
أبي أمي!
Mom!
أم!
Dad!
أب!
Don't call me Dad.
لا تدعوني أبي.
Deep down,
في العمق،
you never really treated me like your dad.
أنت لم تعاملني أبدًا مثل والدك.
It's not like that.
ليس الأمر كذلك.
Then what is it like?
ثم ما هو مثل؟
Just now, in front of so many people,
الآن، أمام الكثير من الناس،
you made me lose so much face.
لقد جعلتني أفقد الكثير من وجهي.
I'm at this age.
أنا في هذا العمر.
It's bad enough I can't enjoy a good life,
إنه أمر سيء بما فيه الكفاية أنني لا أستطيع الاستمتاع بحياة جيدة،
but I also have to
ولكن لا بد لي أيضا من
make a fool of myself in public for you.
أجعل من نفسي أضحوكة في الأماكن العامة من أجلك.
And you,
وأنت
you never call,
أنت لا تتصل أبداً،
but when you do,
ولكن عندما تفعل،
you just ask for money.
أنت فقط تطلب المال.
How did it become my fault?
كيف أصبح خطأي؟
For all these years,
طوال هذه السنوات،
I haven't asked the family for a single penny.
لم أطلب من العائلة مقابل فلس واحد.
I've always tried my best to help out when the family was in trouble.
لقد بذلت دائمًا قصارى جهدي للمساعدة عندما كانت الأسرة في ورطة.
You said you wanted to open a guesthouse,
قلت أنك تريد فتح دار ضيافة،
and you didn't have enough money,
ولم يكن لديك ما يكفي من المال،
so you needed to take out a loan in my name.
لذلك كنت في حاجة إليها للحصول على قرض باسمي.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
I'll take out the loan.
سأحصل على القرض.
The guesthouse just opened,
تم افتتاح بيت الضيافة للتو،
and business wasn't good,
ولم يكن العمل جيداً،
so I've been helping to pay off the loan.
لذلك كنت أساعد في سداد القرض.
You both know that.
كلاكما تعرف ذلك.
What do you mean by this?
ماذا تقصد بهذا؟
Are you trying to settle scores with me now?
هل تحاول لتصفية الحسابات معي الآن؟
Fine.
بخير.
Let's get things straight.
دعونا نضع الأمور في نصابها الصحيح.
Although I'm not your biological father,
على الرغم من أنني لست والدك البيولوجي،
you've been in this family since you were little.
لقد كنت في هذه العائلة منذ أن كنت صغيرا.
I provided you with food and clothes,
قدمت لك الطعام والملابس،
and paid for your college.
ودفع ثمن كليتك.
Right?
يمين؟
So is it wrong for you to help out
فهل من الخطأ أن تساعد
the family now?
العائلة الآن؟
We're not asking you for a fortune.
نحن لا نطلب منك ثروة.
You finally married a good man.
لقد تزوجت أخيرا رجلا طيبا.
But look at what you've done
لكن انظر ماذا فعلت
to this family.
لهذه العائلة.
You did
لقد فعلت
choose a life that made you happy.
اختر الحياة التي جعلتك سعيدا.
But when you chose this life,
ولكن عندما اخترت هذه الحياة،
did you ever consider
هل فكرت يوما
the family that raised you?
العائلة التي ربتك؟
And you even...
وأنت حتى...
How much you've spoiled your daughter!
كم أفسدت ابنتك!
He's your stepfather,
إنه زوج أمك،
but I'm your biological mother.
ولكن أنا والدتك البيولوجية.
It's not easy for us to live
ليس من السهل علينا أن نعيش
under other's roof.
تحت سقف الآخر.
I've told you since you were little
قلت لك منذ كنت صغيرا
to be caring
أن أهتم
and grateful.
وممتن.
Why don't you understand?
لماذا لا تفهم؟
I'm telling you,
أنا أقول لك،
you need to get it straight.
تحتاج إلى الحصول عليها مباشرة.
Don't ask your dad
لا تسأل والدك
for 5,000 yuan every month anymore.
مقابل 5000 يوان كل شهر بعد الآن.
Mom,
أمي،
that 5,000 yuan...
أن 5000 يوان...
I didn't
لم أفعل
borrow the money for myself.
اقتراض المال لنفسي.
Why are you still dawdling?
لماذا لا تزال تتسكع؟
Yourself.
نفسك.
All
الكل
you know is yourself.
أنت تعرف هو نفسك.
You had the guts to get a divorce.
كان لديك الشجاعة للحصول على الطلاق.
Why don't you have the guts to make money?
لماذا لا تملك الشجاعة لكسب المال؟
Coming!
آت!
Jeez.
جيز.